(grand orchestral fanfare
playing)
♪ ♪
Can you pull over?
(grunting)
KENNA:
Dear Scotty:
So. I'm out early
for good behavior.
and here I am. stealing this.
You always hated memorials.
and now I hate them. too.
I hope it's not bad karma.
because I'm headed back
to the place it all went wrong.
See if I can
get something right.
-(indistinct chatter)
-(baby crying)
(grunts softly)
(kitten meows)
RUTH: 550 a month.
First and last today.
No lease.
(kittens squeaking)
-What's your name?
-Kenna Rowan.
(electric guitar playing
rock music in distance)
(sighs)
Shut it. Doug!
-(music stops)
-DOUG: Bitch!
RUTH:
Water and sewer are covered.
There's a $250 deposit
for electric.
T-Two hundred and fifty
on top of two months' rent?
And take a kitten.
A kitten?
Yeah. a kitten.
It's like a cat but smaller.
-Well. I don't want a kitten.
-Who wouldn't want a kitten?
Me.
RUTH: I'll make you a deal.
You take a kitten.
and I'll leave the electric on
for three weeks.
Give you a chance
to get your shit together.
Fine.
Here.
(kitten meows)
(kitten squeaking)
♪ ♪
KENNA:
Remember how we used to wonder
what this place was like?
Well. Paradise is no paradise.
And my new roommate
is a small cat.
What am I gonna do with you?
(sighs)
Now I just need a job
so I can stay here.
make this place a home.
Maybe then
they'll let me see her.
Yeah. well. I'm hungry. too.
(squeaks)
DIEM:
Did you used to paint your nails
when you were in the MFL?
LEDGER:
(chuckles) The NFL.
DIEM:
Oh. NFL.
You need to be pretty
for going to work.
It's very. very important.
right?
Not as important
as being kind and smart.
-Mm. If you say so.
-(chuckles softly)
GRACE:
Diem.
Come on. sweetie.
it's time to come home.
You got to let Ledger
get to work.
Finished.
Thanks. D. (blows)
This is perfect.
All right. let's get you home.
Dragons hold hands
when they cross the street.
Dragons don't have hands. silly.
They have wings.
(Ledger chuckles)
-Come here. Oh!
-Oh. All right.
Thanks.
LEDGER:
Thanks for the visit. D.
-Love you.
-Bye. Love you. too.
-GRACE: Gave him a manicure?
-DIEM: Hmm.
♪ ♪
What the...
-Hey.
Oh. What's got your manties
in a bunch?
-(Mary Anne sighs)
-ROMAN: Afternoon.
-What's up?
-Hola.
(chuckles):
Hey.
-Got your favorite.
-Let me guess. Is it a mug?
More Broncos swag? Seriously?
-Must be Wednesday.
-(Ledger sighs)
It might be worth
drinking again.
Just to end this torture.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah.
Which mug would you use?
STD awareness mug. Yeah.
-It's a favorite.
-(laughs) Nice choice.
While you're obliterating
your liver.
you might as well keep
one eye on your chlamydia.
ROMAN:
Priorities.
-(laughter)
-Funny.
MARY ANNE:
I thought it was funny.
So. what is it? (sniffs)
Scotty's memorial's gone.
-Someone took it?
-Yep.
Who would do something
like that?
-Do you happen to be hiring?
-No.
(birds chirping)
♪ ♪
Hey. uh. are you hiring?
-No. I'm sorry.
-Okay. Thank you.
(entry bells jingling)
(sighs heavily)
Hey.
MRS. BURKE:
Come on in.
(lively chatter)
No. thanks. I just wanted
to see if you needed help.
(sighs) Desperately.
(chuckles) Here. sit.
I'll get an application.
CHILD:
Can I have some more fries?
("Passenger Seat" by Upstate
playing over speakers)
-Here we go.
-Thank you.
♪ We can wave goodbye ♪
-♪ Honey. you can count on me ♪
-CHILD: Can I have some more?
FATHER:
Use your fork.
♪ Never let you down. I'll be ♪
♪ With you
in the passenger seat ♪
♪ Come along for the ride ♪
♪ Anywhere you want... ♪
Oh. we can't hire folks
with a record. hon.
It's policy.
Okay.
Been burned too many times.
Why don't you try
the Dollar Den.
They're always looking.
("The Night We Met"
by Lord Huron playing)
(singers vocalizing)
-(door opens)
-(entry bells jingling)
Hello.
♪ ♪
Just that.
(clears throat)
(register keys
clicking and beeping)
Come back soon.
If you insist.
♪ I've been searching
for a trail... ♪
You know. you can buy
more than one thing at a time.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
I'm just working up the courage
to ask you out. Kenna.
Well. um. Scotty...
-Mm-hmm.
-...it's. um. unfortunately
against store policy for
employees to date customers.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Can I see that?
Excuse me.
Um. I'd just like
to return these plates.
CLERK:
Oh. sure.
SCOTTY:
And. uh...
I'm never shopping here again.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
(Scotty clears throat)
So...
...can I take you to dinner?
In that thing?
You don't like it?
It's just about the ugliest
color orange I've ever seen.
(chuckles) I know.
It's not mine.
It's my best friend's.
I get off at 7:00.
-(song fades)
-(vehicle passing)
KENNA: Everything here
reminds me of you.
but I have to keep going.
Maybe the bookstore
we loved will help.
I miss their bougie coffee.
And I miss you.
Love. Kenna.
-♪ Ballad that you'd play ♪
-(lively chatter)
♪ While you swore to God
the singer read your mind ♪
♪ But the world is scared
of hesitating things ♪
♪ Yeah. they only shoot
the birds ♪
-♪ Who cannot sing... ♪
-(billiard balls clacking)
Who the hell turned
this bookstore into a bar?
I did.
(sighs) What can I get you?
A coffee.
Coffee? Sure.
Uh. cream and sugar okay?
Could you do. um. caramel
and extra foam. please?
You bet.
Soy. skim. almond or whole milk?
Whole's fine.
I was kidding.
Uh. this is a bar.
I do have
a four-hour-old pot of coffee
and your choice
of cream. sugar. both or none.
I'll just take whatever.
Okay.
Uh... (clears throat)
Whatever. coming right up.
♪ I hope you marry rich ♪
♪ I hope you're scared
of only ordinary shit ♪
♪ Like murderers and ghosts
and cancer on your skin ♪
♪ And not your soul
and what he might do with it ♪
♪ Ah-oh. ♪
("One and Only" by Dhruv
playing over speakers)
♪ Oh. darling ♪
♪ My words are overflowing ♪
(women laughing and chattering)
♪ Drenched in new emotion ♪
♪ I gotta be
right where you are ♪
♪ With timing... ♪
I'll take my usual.
I got you. Stacey.
♪ There's no way of knowing ♪
♪ So I'll steal this moment ♪
♪ To tell you it
straight from the heart... ♪
Pretty impressive for
not a coffee shop.
Well. I'll be the judge of that.
♪ I've got your favorite song
on play ♪
♪ I'm reminiscing on the train ♪
♪ Said I'm a couple... ♪
Well. I'd probably give it. um.
a solid three stars on Yelp.
-Three?
-Mm.
That reaction was more like
a four. four and a half.
Well. um. no caramel. so...
No caramel.
Got it. Okay.
It's good to have something
to aim for.
What were you writing?
(clears throat)
Um. nothing.
Ooh. Uh...
Hey. do you happen to be hiring?
I could. um. up your Yelp game.
(chuckles) Not right now.
Sorry.
STACEY: Hey. Coach.
Question about tomorrow's game.
Uh. I'll be right back.
What's up?
Uh. not a good pass.
-STACEY: I get it.
-LEDGER: Uh. yeah.
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
-Anyways. I got work to do.
so... -(women laughing)
How's Skylar doing? She's good?
(conversation continues
indistinctly)
-Those two right there?
-Yeah.
(door opens. closes)
♪ Anticipation on the train ♪
-(sighs)
-(billiard balls clacking)
♪ Said I'm another stop away ♪
♪ Yeah. I'm talking... ♪
(muffled music continues inside)
(sniffs)
(crickets chirping)
(gasps softly)
(whispers):
Oh. shit.
("Mud" by Waxahatchee
playing over speakers)
-♪ Singing. "I'm not the one" ♪
-(lively chatter)
♪ Not your haven at the bottom ♪
♪ Or some
miserable companion... ♪
Uh. I left my. um...
-Oh. right. It's in the back.
-Oh.
Thank you.
♪ In your storm garbage ♪
♪ Weather worn... ♪
I didn't read it. (sighs)
Promise.
-Um...
-(chuckles softly)
I could walk you out back.
It's closer.
Okay. Yeah.
-Um. wait. um...
-(dog barking in distance)
(Ledger clears throat)
(sighs) You. uh...
you mind if I get your number?
I... (chuckles)
Uh. I don't have a phone.
(clears throat)
(Ledger laughs)
Who doesn't have a phone?
I should. uh.
I should probably go.
Um. you should stay.
-(door opens) -ROMAN:
Hey. Ledger. need you inside.
LEDGER:
One sec.
(door closes)
You okay?
-I have to go.
-Yeah.
Come back tomorrow.
I'll-I'll have that caramel.
I just-- I can't. okay?
Yeah.
(breathing heavily)
(dog barking in distance)
(squeaks)
(muffled TV chatter in distance)
(kitten meowing)
♪ ♪
KENNA:
Dear Scotty:
I met your friend Ledger today.
He didn't recognize me.
but why would he?
It's not like we ever met.
I'm gonna keep my distance.
-GRACE: Happy birthday.
-PATRICK: Happy birthday.
KENNA:
I have enough to figure out.
Especially with Grace.
SCOTTY: Ledger said
he was gonna be here.
He also knew it was important.
It's a make-or-break game
this week.
I'm sure he wants to be here.
There's always something.
Hey. why don't we go out.
do something fun?
-Now?
-KENNA: I've had years
to imagine how she must feel.
Uh. yeah. Go. Go.
KENNA:
She didn't want you to leave.
We should have listened.
(knocking on door)
If we did. she wouldn't have
heard words like "sorry..."
(Grace sighs)
...and "accident"
and "didn't make it."
You were their perfect boy.
In a perfect world.
you'd still be alive.
But instead. they had to live
in a world without you.
Because of me.
I'm the one they blame.
And I understand why.
JUDGE:
You have pled guilty
to vehicular manslaughter
under the influence.
This court accepts
your guilty plea
and sentences you
to seven years' incarceration.
(crying softly)
KENNA:
And yet. here I am.
back in their lives.
asking for one thing:
to meet our daughter.
SINGERS (over TV):
♪ Meow... ♪
GRACE:
(sighs) Yes.
-Uh. I can hold.
-(door opens)
-LEDGER: Diem!
-(door closes)
It's time for T-ball.
Go get dressed.
We got to go!
Is that Scotty's old jungle gym?
That was our spot.
GRACE: It's what she wanted
for her birthday.
Well. of course it is.
DIEM:
Ledger. help me!
I can't find my other boot.
Boots? Wear your cleats.
-People don't wear boots
to play T-ball. -I am.
-I'm wearing my boots today.
-Listen to your coach.
No burger
if you don't wear your cleats.
-Found your other boot.
-(chuckles)
-Is that a freakin' pigeon?
-(laughs)
(both grunting playfully)
(chuckles) You win.
When's my mom getting
a bigger car?
She drives a minivan.
How big a car does she need?
Not Nana. My mom.
What do you mean?
Skylar says my mom never comes
to my T-ball games.
but when I ask Nana.
she says she will
when she gets a bigger car.
Mm.
Well. let me talk to Nana
about that. but we got to go.
We're late.
(groaning playfully)
(Diem laughing)
-Her mom needs a bigger car?
-(sighs) I know.
And I. uh...
I'm not prepared for her
to start asking.
I'm not ready.
Have you thought about
telling her the truth?
-No. she's five.
-(chuckles) Yeah.
And she won't stop asking
till she knows.
-(keys jangling)
-(engine starts)
Bye. Have a good game.
♪ ♪
MANAGER: This is
a family-owned supermarket
that puts our customers
on a pedestal.
Uh. nothing is more important.
Consequently. we have to know
at every level of interface
that we can guarantee
our customers' happiness.
And...
safety.
Okay. (sighs)
-(grunts softly. sighs)
-(door closes)
AMY:
Hey.
(Amy sniffling)
Are you okay?
I just... (sniffles)
rear-ended someone.
and I don't have insurance.
(sniffles)
What's your trauma?
Well. I can't get a job because
I just got out of prison.
Really? (sniffles)
Yep. (sighs)
Shit. you win.
Yay. me.
What kind of job
are you looking for?
I mean. honestly. anything.
Well. I can't guarantee
full-time.
but I could give you
some shifts as a bagger.
Manager already said no.
I could talk to him.
-Amy Matthews.
-Kenna.
Assistant manager.
recent rear-ender.
in charge of checkouts
and bagging.
-Thank you.
-I wouldn't go booking
any trips on a private jet
this side of Christmas.
The hours are shit.
and pay's even shittier.
Hey. don't you live
in Paradise apartments?
-Can you start Monday?
-(girl humming a tune)
Yes. (sighs)
Thank you.
(door opens. closes)
(sighs)
(water stops)
(chuckles softly)
♪ ♪
(door opens. closes)
What's Tinder?
(laughs)
Where'd you hear that?
Skylar's mom said
if you have it.
she'll break her finger.
-(laughing)
-(snorts)
♪ ♪
(dog barking in distance)
(car door closes)
DIEM:
Nana. I'm a burger monster.
GRACE (playful voice):
Well. you better eat the burger
before it eats you.
LEDGER:
Guys. I'm headed out.
-GRACE (normal voice):
Okay. bye. -Love you. D.
Love you. too.
Hey.
How'd you know
I lived around here?
Um...
Well. I'm not here to see you.
Then why are you here?
♪ ♪
You're Kenna.
I-I need to see her.
-Go. Right now.
-(panting)
-This is none of your business.
-The hell it isn't.
Ledger. please.
Please just let me
speak to them.
-LEDGER: Goddamn.
-You don't understand. okay?
LEDGER:
Yeah.
Just get inside.
Sit.
Sit down.
A teething ring?
She's five.
What are you thinking
showing up here?
She's my daughter.
Diem is their daughter.
Your rights were terminated.
Goddamn.
(both panting)
I'm pulling the truck in
the garage and taking you home.
Don't move. I mean it.
-(keys jangling)
-(door opens)
(door closes)
♪ ♪
Hey.
-(knocks)
-Open the door!
Get your hands off me!
(both grunting)
-Get off of me.
-Calm down.
You can't be here.
Don't touch me.
-Grace. shut the door.
-What's going on?
Everything's fine.
Hey.
Get in the truck.
I'll call the police.
(both panting)
♪ ♪
Coming back was a mistake.
No one benefits from you being
in Diem's life except you.
You're an asshole.
Fuck you!
(panting)
(grunting angrily)
(sighs)
(pained screaming)
(crying)
(grunting)
-(baby crying)
-(breathing heavily)
(baby continues crying)
KENNA:
Wait. Where are you taking her?
Where is she going? No!
(door closes)
(soft clattering)
(door opens)
(door closes)
Why don't you have any stuff?
I just moved in.
Can I have this?
Sure.
(gasps)
You got a kitten?
Can you go. please? (sighs)
Mom won't let me have one.
-What's its name?
-It doesn't have a name yet.
(sighs)
Why are you so poor?
(laughs)
I... just got out of prison.
My dad's in prison.
Do you know him?
I was in a women's prison.
so no.
Why are you so sad?
I have a daughter. and
no one's letting me see her.
(gasps) Did she get kidnapped?
(chuckles) No. no.
She's with her grandparents.
but they're not
letting me see her.
But you want to?
More than anything.
I'm Lady Diana.
I have some sparklers.
Do you want
to light them with me?
Maybe later?
(door opens)
(door closes)
MAN:
Rec room closes in 15 minutes.
(door buzzes)
-(inmates chattering)
-(indistinct radio chatter)
(indistinct announcement
over P.A.)
Come with me. I'm Ivy.
MAN (over P.A.):
Rec room closes in ten minutes.
Start heading back
to your bunks.
Boy or girl?
Was a girl.
They gonna let you see her?
MAN (over P.A.): All inmates
and COs be advised...
Don't know.
(hand dryer whirring)
They took your baby from you.
You're never gonna
get over that.
So. you decide.
right here. right now.
You gonna live in your sadness
or you gonna die in it?
I'm gonna live in it.
(kitten squeaks)
I'm gonna name you Ivy.
(Grace stammers)
How could she just show up?
I hope you told her
to leave town.
-She is not welcome here.
-Of course I did.
GRACE: I can't believe
she's out already.
Diem almost saw her.
Let me go say good night to D
before I head to work.
I got to call our lawyer.
GRACE:
Oh. God.
You good?
Yep.
Kenna's back.
-Diem's mom?
-Yep. (sighs) She was the woman
sitting at the end of the bar
the other night.
(chuckles) No shit.
-You didn't recognize her?
-Nope.
Never met her.
I thought he was. like.
your best friend.
(sighs)
Yeah. but I wasn't around.
I saw her mug shot once.
But. uh. she looked
completely different then.
I don't know.
Patrick and Grace
don't need this right now.
I mean. to be fair.
she did give birth to D.
Yeah. but no parent should be
forced to set up visitation
with their son's murderer.
Don't you think "murderer"
is a bit dramatic?
She's not
some stone-cold killer.
She left him there.
Ledge. if it weren't for you.
I'd be lying
in a ditch somewhere.
Maybe she's operating
in the same gray area I was.
So. what. she's in the gray.
and now you want to be
all black and white?
It's not like you.
Want some seeds?
You're an asshole.
(chuckles)
("Bright Star"
by Anaïs Mitchell playing)
(sighs)
♪ Bright star ♪
♪ I've sailed
in all directions ♪
♪ I've followed
your reflection ♪
♪ To the farthest
foreign shore ♪
♪ Bright star. bright star ♪
♪ I have anchored
in the harbor ♪
♪ I have brought
my gifts to barter ♪
♪ For a drifter's bed
and board ♪
♪ Bright star ♪
♪ I have drunk
the wine of ages ♪
♪ In the company of strangers ♪
♪ We have sung
in tongues of angels ♪
♪ And then stumbled
on the pavement ♪
♪ And I understood
my place then ♪
♪ And my purpose in relation ♪
♪ To the young
and ancient night. ♪
(sighs)
(song fades)
Why are you here?
I just wanted to see
if you were okay.
(scoffs)
Wait.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
But that's not it.
really. is it?
You're worried that if you hear
that I ended my life
while you're eating
your cornflakes in the morning.
you might be left
feeling guilty.
That it was because of you.
But don't worry. You did it.
Your conscience is clear.
-(sharp thump on window)
-(gasps) Oh. my God.
Roll down the window.
Are you Kenna's dad?
(laughing)
-Okay. he's...
-Uh...
He's definitely not my dad.
No.
He's the guy who won't let me
meet my daughter.
-Jerk.
-(truck door closes)
Thank you for being on my side.
PATRICK: Our lawyer
told us there's nothing
she can do legally.
Legally is not the issue.
I'm worried she's gonna swipe
her when no one's looking.
PATRICK:
We can't trust her.
I don't know. I don't think
she'd do something like that.
Wh-What do you mean? (stammers)
How would you know
what she would do?
We don't know
what she's capable of.
None of us know her. right?
Maybe you should meet up with
her. see what she has to say?
(scoffs) What would
she possibly have to s-say?
PATRICK:
Ledge. no. She's got no rights.
-Y-You know how hard this
has been. okay? -(Grace sighs)
We're finally in a good place.
We're not sharing Scotty's
daughter with the woman...
My horse's head came off.
-PATRICK: Uh-oh.
-Oh. boy.
-(chuckles)
-How did that happen?
I pulled it off.
GRACE: Yeah. Well.
it's not a surprise. then.
Here. let's go.
Sorry. Patrick.
I didn't mean to overstep.
No. no. no.
Just make yourself useful.
No worries.
Just bring that wood over.
Yes. sir.
You want to know
something funny?
You know Scotty had
his first kiss up here?
Yeah. he told me that.
Who was it? Dana?
Yep. (sighs)
I remember I was pissed.
Called dibs on her first.
Well. he's much better looking
than you are.
(both chuckle)
Yeah. He was.
(Ledger sighs)
I'm gonna get a beer.
You want one?
Yeah. I'll take one.
♪ ♪
(Scotty laughs)
LEDGER:
When I'm older...
SCOTTY:
Uh-huh.
...I'm gonna put the "L" in NFL.
-I hate you so much.
-(snickering)
Team?
(inhales deeply)
Broncos.
Now you're talking.
I'm more of
a simple-life kind of guy.
My plan is to get married.
be a dad.
That's what I'm gonna do.
While you go off
and take down Brady.
Wait.
-What?
-What is that?
What?
What the hell?
SCOTTY:
What?
Is that a freakin' pigeon?
That?
Yes.
-(laughing): A freakin' pigeon?
-(laughing)
That's my baseball glove.
(both laughing)
That's my freakin'
baseball glove.
-Holy-- Oh!
-(gasps)
(both laughing)
And who says "freakin'." anyway?
You're so freakin' high.
-(indistinct chatter)
-(scanners beeping)
Oh. super!
♪ ♪
Kenna. I need you on two.
Do you have bags?
No bags.
♪ ♪
Does she look like me?
(Ledger sighs)
Yeah. she does.
What's she like?
-(Kenna sighs)
-(thunder rumbling)
Do you walk to work?
Yeah.
Got an umbrella?
Nope.
You could call a Uber. (sighs)
Did they have Uber before you...
Went to prison? Yeah.
Yeah. they had Uber.
Still don't have a phone.
(Ledger clears throat)
Jerk.
(Kenna laughing)
(Ledger clears throat)
("Stand by Me" by
Stephen Wilson Jr. playing)
♪ When the night ♪
♪ The night has come ♪
(thunder rumbling softly)
♪ And all the land is dark ♪
♪ And the moon ♪
♪ Is the only light we'll see ♪
♪ No. I won't be afraid ♪
♪ No. I won't shed
a single tear ♪
♪ Just as long as you.
just as long as you ♪
♪ Stand by me ♪
-(gasps)
-♪ So won't you stand ♪
♪ By me? ♪
♪ Won't you. won't you ♪
♪ Stand by me. stand by me? ♪
♪ Won't you stand... ♪
(breathing heavily)
("Deep in Love" by
Bonny Light Horseman playing)
Is that a freakin' pigeon?
♪ Deep to the line... ♪
You okay?
(sighs)
Just a little bit of rain.
-You need a ride home?
-No. I'm fine.
I'll just wait it out.
It's a slow night.
Let me give you a ride.
It's fine. (sighs)
(chuckles)
All right.
♪ Break my heart... ♪
(sighs)
No wonder no one's in here.
The music's miserable.
I thought misery loved company.
Misery loves no music
because all music is miserable.
But I heard
misery loves caramel.
Oh. could I get it
in a to-go cup?
Don't push it.
Still not a coffee shop.
Are you sure
you don't want a ride?
Did you show up
to my bar that night
because you wanted me
to lead you to her?
No. I only showed up
because it was the bookstore
Scotty and I loved.
I had no idea who you were
until I heard your name.
because you were never around.
(Kenna sniffles)
So you're telling me...
What?
Scotty knew what a book was?
(chuckles)
Thank you for the ride.
And the caramel.
LEDGER: Did you say
you're going to propose?
SCOTTY (over phone):
You heard me correct.
(chuckles) Don't you think
it's a little too soon?
No. No. I don't think
it's too soon.
I love her.
I'm gonna ask her
on my birthday.
-and I want you to be there.
Okay? -MAN: Hey. two-seven.
-Let's make moves.
-SCOTTY: Ledge.
Hey. hey.
Promise me.
You're gonna love her.
I promise I'll be there.
I got to run. all right?
All right. Bye.
LEDGER:
What'd you say?
DIEM (over phone):
What are you doing?
Working.
No. you're not.
You're drinking a soda.
(sighs) What do you know
about work?
-How many jobs have you had?
-(chuckles)
I'm a kid!
And what are you up to. kid?
Going grocery shopping
with Nana.
Oh. yeah? What store?
What s-- Diem! (sighs)
(line ringing)
♪ ♪
(tires squealing)
-(indistinct chatter)
-(scanners beeping)
-What are we gonna get
on our fruit platter? -Cheese.
-Cheese on our fruit platter?
-(chuckles)
(tires squealing)
Grace!
-Ledger!
-Hold up! Hold up. hold up.
-What?
-Get her back to the car. Now.
-Come on. Come on. Come on.
-I can walk. you know.
♪ ♪
Grace!
Grace. please!
(tires screech)
Please!
(grunts) Why did you do that?!
Why the hell did you do that?!
(panting)
AMY:
Everything okay?
Just go.
-You need to take some time?
-I'm sorry. I...
I'll deal with him.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-Okay. (sniffles)
(panting)
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Kenna!
Kenna. Get in.
Kenna. Can we talk?
(Ledger sighs)
(Kenna sniffles)
Other mothers told me
what it would be like.
I'd be taken to the hospital
to give birth
and that I would get
two days with her.
Two whole days. just me and her.
It was the only thing
I had to look forward to.
(sighs)
But she was born early.
Um. six weeks.
I don't know if you knew that.
Her lungs weren't
fully developed.
so they rushed her to the NICU.
While I had to spend
those two days alone.
(sniffles)
I never got to hold her.
-Kenna. I...
-Please don't.
(sniffles)
It was stupid to...
assume that they would just
let me be a part of her life.
I didn't come here because
I think that I deserve her.
But. God. I just...
(sniffles)
I want to meet the human that...
...that Scotty and I made.
(sniffles. sighs)
(sighs)
(sniffles)
(sighs heavily)
(inhales deeply)
Ants in my pants
make my belly button dance.
-Your turn. Ledger.
-(Kenna chuckles)
Say. "Ants in my pants
make my belly button dance."
LEDGER (over video):
All right.
-Ants in my pants
make my belly... -(chuckles)
DIEM: It's a good thing
that I made you...
made you check
your belly button. right?
LEDGER (over video):
Oh. Whoa.
What you doing? All right.
-Oh! Don't fall.
-(chuckles. sniffles)
Mmm. Aw.
(breathing heavily)
(sniffles) She's amazing.
Thank you.
-Yeah.
-(sniffles)
DIEM: It's a good thing
that I made you...
-made you check your belly
button. right? -(both chuckle)
♪ ♪
Can I ask you something?
Do you hate me?
You know. the...
other night
when we met at the bar.
I thought you were.
I don't know. intriguing.
Then the next day in front of
Patrick and Grace's. I...
...thought you were
the worst person ever.
And what about now?
Now... (sighs)
I'm starting to wonder
if you're the saddest girl
I've ever met.
All of the above. I guess.
(chuckles softly. sniffles)
Yeah. we should. uh...
I'll take the...
Are you done with that?
(Ledger sighs)
(engine starts)
It wasn't a good look. you know.
Uh. to his parents.
to the judge.
to anybody in that courtroom.
They told me
you just seemed so...
I seemed so what?
Unremorseful.
Unremorseful?
I was broken.
Scotty was the closest thing
to a home that I ever had.
♪ ♪
Sometimes I get the urge
to take her.
You know?
But obviously
I'm not gonna do that.
I... just want to prove
to Grace and Patrick
that I'm responsible.
Well. I want to be ready
for when they let me meet her.
And what if that day
doesn't come?
Well. I have to live
in hope that it will.
But I can. uh.
barely pay my rent.
(sighs) Yeah.
Um... (sniffs)
What if you come
and work for me?
For you?
Fridays and Saturdays.
Um. obviously in the back.
That way. no one has to know.
Are you being serious?
Yes.
-(Kenna sniffles)
-Okay.
Hey. come at 4:00 on Friday.
("September Fields"
by Frazey Ford playing)
(sighs)
♪ You better get up
for your mama ♪
♪ You better grab
the best of your life ♪
♪ I know you're ready ♪
♪ To get older ♪
♪ Anyhow... ♪
RUTH: Sick of having
this conversation with you.
DOUG: You do nothing
but complain and complain.
You can't evict me
for making art.
Electric guitar at midnight
isn't art.
It's a violation of your lease.
I didn't sign a lease.
Did you sign anything
when you moved in?
RUTH:
You leave her out of it. Doug.
She took a kitten.
The rules don't apply.
As long as
I keep paying my rent.
I'm gonna keep playing
my guitar.
Maybe if you play something she
likes. she won't get as mad.
She was born mad.
-I like the ukulele!
-DOUG: You would.
(laughs)
♪ And turn and turn at night? ♪
♪ And are you holding ♪
-♪ Holding on so tight? ♪
-(song fades)
♪ ♪
-(panting)
-(knocks)
Hey. I'm Kenna.
Uh. reporting for duty.
I'm sorry. I forgot to tell you.
She's gonna help us out
in the back. Um...
Uh. this is Roman. Um...
ROMAN:
Okay.
Uh. unexpected.
Um. do you... do you know
how to wash dishes?
Six years' experience.
Okay. I'm not... I'm not gonna
ask you to elaborate on that.
LEDGER:
I'm sorry. I got to go.
Um. can you show her around?
I'll be back. (sighs)
-Follow me. This way.
-Okay.
-(lively chatter) -♪ Yeah.
when you're giving me love... ♪
(music and chatter continue
faintly in distance)
Wow. I haven't seen this floor
in a long-ass time.
-Or my shoes. for that matter.
-(chuckles)
-Uh. do you want a drink?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-Whew! Oh. man.
-(can opens)
Can I ask you something?
Mm-hmm.
Who is this. uh. Leah?
Leah is Ledger's ex-fiancée.
They broke up about a year ago.
Wow. I had no idea. (sighs)
She wanted to be
the only girl in his life.
-He cheated?
-No.
She was jealous of Diem.
Diem's like
his-his pseudo niece.
It's hard to explain.
But he is hopelessly devoted
to that little girl.
MARY ANNE: ...hang out
at my place sometime?
(Kenna chuckles)
MARY ANNE:
It's my third.
When you meet my husband.
you'll know why.
He's a lightning rod.
Kenna has revolutionized
this place.
ROMAN: And she found
the Cold Creek order.
LEDGER:
Oh. This is good.
This is great. actually. Thanks.
Roman. I'm leaving you to close.
-That cool?
-Yep.
Uh. need a ride home?
Yeah. sure.
How come her job
comes with perks?
See you. guys.
-He ever give you a ride home?
-No.
♪ ♪
Does she ever ask about me?
She doesn't really understand
family dynamics yet.
so she doesn't really think
anyone's missing from her life.
Right now. she thinks
you're not in her life because
your car's not big enough.
(chuckles)
What?
(laughs):
Yeah. I know.
It's. uh... it's a long story.
Can you tell me what she's like?
She loves animals.
Especially dogs.
She hates peanut butter
but loves snow cones.
And she...
she has a fiery spirit.
Just like you.
I'm sorry about. uh...
is it Leah?
-Wow. Mary Anne works fast.
-Mm.
To be fair. um. I learned
most of my info from Scotty.
Oh. yeah? Like what?
Well. I know that you both cried
watching Princess Diaries.
Oh. my God.
(Kenna laughs)
He would always say
that catchphrase.
It's... "damn pigeon."
or something.
It's actually "freakin' pigeon."
(laughs)
Now we're uneven.
I need to know more on you.
What do you want to know?
What do you write about
in your notebook?
What do you say in therapy?
(chuckles):
I don't go to therapy.
-Well. maybe you should.
-(chuckles)
(Kenna laughs)
I write letters to Scotty.
Did you write about that night?
Yes.
-(button clicks)
-Uh. can you not play music?
Why?
I just-- I don't like it.
It's all... sad.
and everyone's in pain.
(chuckles):
Okay.
Well. let's see.
♪ Jesus Christ.
I'm so blue all the time... ♪
See?
-That's sad.
-All right. let's...
(radio station changes)
♪ I'm all out of love ♪
♪ What am I without you... ♪
(Ledger laughs)
-There you go.
-(radio station changes)
-♪ So lo-o-o-onely ♪
-(both laughing)
♪ Lo-o-o-onely... ♪
(laughs)
-Yeah. let's just turn that off.
-(radio clicks off)
(both laughing)
-KENNA: Hey. How are you guys?
-Hi.
This is my mom.
-She's never been to prison.
-Oh.
(both laughing)
I wanted to let you know
that we are having
a Mother's Day lunch
in a couple of weeks
in the courtyard.
Come. It'll be fun.
It's a potluck.
Um...
-Yeah. Okay.
-Yeah.
I-I would love to.
If you have any extra chairs.
we never have enough.
She doesn't even have a bed.
It was nice meeting you.
-(lively chatter)
-♪ Before I met you. dear ♪
♪ I couldn't face my fears ♪
♪ I was insincere.
there was... ♪
(chatter and music continue
faintly in distance)
ROMAN:
Oh. it's busy.
You okay?
-(sighs): Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah?
Uh. I wanted to ask
if. um. you guys had
any spare. like. tables
or chairs that I could borrow?
Yeah. I think so.
I could show you real fast.
-Okay. Yeah. Thank you.
-Yeah?
Uh... (sighs) Yeah.
-Oh. yeah. Perfect.
-Yeah?
-Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
KENNA:
So. what's with all the mugs?
Someone have a coffee addiction?
Uh. alcohol. actually.
-Oh. God. I'm so sorry.
-(laughs) No.
-Bad... bad joke.
-No. you're good.
No. there's no secrets here.
Every week. to commemorate my
sobriety. Ledger gets me a mug.
-That's nice.
-Yeah.
Must be hard working
in a bar. though.
Mm. sometimes.
It would be
if he actually did any work.
You guys are aware
it's Friday night. right?
I'm sorry. I asked him for help.
-Yeah. Mm-hmm. Thank you.
-Uh. I'll be back later.
-"You guys are aware it's
Friday night. right?" -Uh-huh.
("Neon Moon" by Brooks & Dunn
with Kacey Musgraves playing)
♪ When the sun goes down
on my side of town ♪
♪ That lonesome feeling
comes to my door ♪
♪ And the whole world ♪
♪ Turns blue ♪
♪ I spend most every night ♪
♪ Beneath the light ♪
♪ Of a neon moon ♪
♪ If you lose
your one and only ♪
♪ There's always room here
for the lonely ♪
♪ To watch your broken dreams ♪
♪ Dance in and out
of the beams ♪
♪ Of a neon moon. ♪
LEDGER: Wait. (chuckles)
You got a phone?
Finally.
Look at you. (chuckles)
Here.
(Ledger sighs)
Give me your number.
Well. what if I don't want
to give it to you?
Well. I'm your boss. and
I need to call my employees.
Mm. (smacks lips)
Right. Of course.
(camera clicks)
What was that for?
Just in case
I can't place the name.
(Ledger chuckles)
LEDGER:
I want to show you something.
-(phone chirps. dings)
-Check your phone.
It's a playlist.
-I told you that...
-Just look at it.
It's a happy playlist.
Not all music's miserable.
Was that stupid?
Not stupid at all.
♪ ♪
(Ledger sighs)
(Ivy squeaking)
(Ledger grunts)
You sleep on the couch?
I got something for you.
Hang tight. (clears throat)
(door opens)
-(sighs)
-(door closes)
KENNA:
What am I doing. Ivy?
(sighs)
(door opens)
What's. um...
I don't know
if you want this. Uh...
(laughs)
(both laugh)
-This...
-Oh. Oh.
-Wow.
-...is part of my camping gear.
I see you camp like a princess.
(chuckles)
You're the one who stole this?
(sighs)
Seriously. Kenna?
I'm out here betraying everyone
I love by helping you out.
and you're stealing the
one thing made to honor him?
Scotty hated memorials.
I was doing him a favor.
(scoffs) Jesus Christ.
You still think I went
to your bar with an agenda.
Hmm.
Well. I didn't.
You can go now.
(Kenna sighs)
(door opens)
♪ ♪
Goddamn it. Kenna.
(breathing heavily)
We can't. (sighs)
It's just gonna make it
so much worse.
I know.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
(truck door opens. closes)
(engine starts)
(busy chatter)
(scanner beeps)
-CASHIER: That it?
-Yeah.
Is this yours?
Okay.
Thank you.
CASHIER 2:
There.
Kenna Rowan?
Yeah.
You've been served.
(breathes deeply)
♪ ♪
My legs are soaking sore.
(Ledger laughing)
(chuckles):
They're what?
-You and your...
-That was a good game. you.
(Ledger grunts)
GRACE:
Okay. squirmy.
-(Ledger chuckles)
-(Diem grunts)
Okay. All set.
(Grace sighs)
-(indistinct chatter)
-Okay. ready?
How old will I be when you die?
You don't need
to worry about that.
(phone dings)
Ledger?
Everything okay?
Yeah. Um...
Love you. D.
-Thanks.
-Yep.
♪ ♪
(horn honks)
(Ledger sighs)
I can't believe they did this.
If I try and see her again.
they could arrest me.
-(sighs) -They're not
gonna change their minds.
(sighs)
Want to take the night off?
No. I-I can't. I need the hours.
We could show up late.
LEDGER:
How's it going?
(lively chatter)
You want to try Diem's favorite?
-Yeah.
-All right.
I will have one FofanaLemonana.
and then my usual.
-Thank you.
-Oh. boy.
Not even gonna ask.
(both laugh)
I'm picking up
yellow is her favorite color.
(chuckles)
(laughing):
What?
(laughing): You got
a little something right there.
Oh. no.
Well. your tongue's blue.
-It is?
-And your teeth.
And your lips.
(Ledger laughs)
So. why did you move back
to your childhood home?
I blew out my shoulder.
Oh. I'm sorry.
But don't NFL players.
you know. usually get
fancy mansions or a penthouse?
I'm building a house.
It's taken me four years. but...
Jesus. Four years?
I mean. what.
carving it out of stone?
You want to go see it?
I'll take you.
Um...
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-Sure.
-All right.
♪ ♪
(door creaks)
What?
This is insane.
Wow.
(sighs):
Yeah.
Come on.
I'll show you the rest.
Seriously. though.
this is amazing.
So. um. when are you
hoping to move in?
(sighs)
I don't know.
This has been my dream
for a long time.
But then I think about
not seeing Diem every day.
(wind whistling softly)
Then sell it.
Or rent it.
I'd much prefer
you closer to her.
knowing that you're
in her life every day.
It's comforting to me.
But what about you?
What is it that you really want?
I want to do right by her.
I mean. she doesn't have a dad.
And I wasn't there for Scotty.
♪ ♪
You didn't get married
because of her.
You're not moving
You know. you can't live
Scotty's life for him.
♪ ♪
Uh. so I was looking
at the. um. the closet...
-Uh-huh. -...and was thinking
maybe I could rent it.
I mean. it's much bigger than
my current apartment. so...
(Ledger chuckles)
We should go to work.
Mm. yes.
Don't want to piss off the boss.
-♪ Put your heart ♪
-(lively chatter)
♪ In my hand ♪
-♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪ For the right man... ♪
Oh. Thank you so much.
PATRICK:
There he is.
-Hey. hey!
-GRACE: Hi!
(chuckles) We got Skylar's
older sister to babysit.
-We just needed a night out.
Hey. -Hey. guys.
LEDGER: Uh. Mary Anne.
can you take care of them?
(chuckles):
I know. It's crazy.
-PATRICK: Crazy.
-It's busy tonight.
MARY ANNE:
Do you want your regular?
GRACE:
One drink only.
MARY ANNE:
I got you.
You know what? Uh. before I sit.
-is your truck parked out back?
-LEDGER: Yeah. yeah. yeah.
-Diem left her backpack
in there. -I got it. Patrick.
-I'm gonna grab it. I got it.
-Go sit.
-I'm already wet.
-I got you.
It's pouring. You got customers.
Whew!
♪ I can turn
your dark to light ♪
♪ Come on in... ♪
(truck door opens. closes)
Go get a drink with your wife.
("Long Blue Light"
by Leif Vollebekk playing)
(singer vocalizing)
(knock on door)
♪ Mountain of worry... ♪
Thank you.
You know. you could've
texted me that.
Yeah.
(chuckles)
♪ Tell me just one time... ♪
Um...
Why are you here?
(Ledger sighs)
♪ On your side ♪
♪ Long blue light ♪
♪ If you don't call me ♪
♪ I might lose my mind ♪
♪ Can't keep concentrating ♪
♪ On all the worry I find ♪
♪ So just lend me your body ♪
♪ I'll lend you mine ♪
♪ I'm on your side ♪
♪ On your side ♪
♪ Long blue light ♪
You taste like apples.
-And you're cold and wet.
-Mm-hmm.
(breathing heavily)
♪ ♪
♪ My eyelids are heavy ♪
♪ My spirit is numb ♪
♪ Don't know where I'm headed ♪
♪ Don't know where I'm from ♪
♪ I'm here just waiting ♪
♪ For my day to come ♪
♪ I'm on your side ♪
♪ On your side ♪
♪ Long blue light ♪
♪ I'm on your side ♪
♪ On your side ♪
♪ Long blue light. ♪
♪ ♪
(song fades)
(breathing heavily)
♪ ♪
(Ledger sighs)
Hey. you.
What'd you write?
None of your business.
I want to hear it.
Come here.
Don't think
you're gonna like it.
Try me.
"Dear Scotty:
"I had sex with
your best friend tonight.
"I'm not sure it's something
you want to hear.
"Maybe it is.
"I get the feeling.
if you can hear these letters
"wherever you are.
you'd want me to be happy.
"and right now
Ledger is making me happy.
"If it's any consolation.
the sex was great...
...but no one can
hold a candle to you."
(Ledger laughs)
You're just saying that
so you don't hurt his feelings?
(chuckles)
Right?
(smacks lips)
Whatever you need to hear.
Give me that.
-Mm-hmm.
-(sighs)
It was still good. though. no?
(whispers):
The best.
(thunder rumbling)
(both laugh)
Oh. Scotty didn't like that one.
-Mm-mm.
-(laughs)
(Kenna grunts)
(both laughing)
-♪ ♪
-(birds chirping)
DIEM:
It's Ledger!
GRACE:
Oh. yeah.
Okay. all right. Oh. my gosh.
-Ah. My ladybug.
-Geez.
-(grunts)
-Giving me a heart attack.
(chuckles)
-Hey. You good?
-Oh.
You look like maybe you didn't
get enough sleep last night.
I got plenty. Thanks.
Well. it's good timing
'cause she wanted to say hi.
We're going to Grandma Landry's.
Don't forget me. okay?
Well. you're only leaving
for an afternoon. D.
How can I forget about you?
Old people forget stuff.
-(Ledger laughs)
-(chuckles) Come on. you.
-Thanks for that.
-Yeah.
Okay. We'll see him later.
See you later.
Grace. uh. actually.
I almost forgot.
Aw.
Happy Mother's Day.
Thanks.
That was really nice.
-And very pretty. (chuckles)
-(chuckles)
I'm gonna go
put them in water. okay?
-Okay.
-Can you keep an eye?
What's Mother's Day?
(Ledger sighs)
Mother's Day...
(sighs) It's a holiday.
But Nana isn't your mother.
She is not. but I lived
across the street from her
my whole life.
so she's like a mom to me.
Where is your mommy?
She is in Florida.
so I sent her flowers.
I want to get my mommy flowers.
the one with the tiny car.
Your mommy will get flowers. D.
Come on. NoNo and Nana.
We're late.
-We're not late.
-(Ledger chuckles)
Happy Mother's Day. Ledger.
I'm so proud of you.
Love you. crazy girl.
♪ ♪
(lively chatter and laughter)
(cheering)
(lively chatter continues)
To mothers. including Kenna.
even though
her daughter was kidnapped.
-(laughter) -(chuckles)
-To mothers.
-OTHERS: To mothers.
-MAN: Cheers.
(gentle ukulele music playing)
So. what's the deal with Doug?
We used to date.
Turns out I fell for a crazy guy
whose love language
is stupidity.
Hmm.
Stupid crazy for you.
(truck door opens)
-Speaking of stupid crazy.
-(truck door closes)
I'm gonna... Yep. Um...
Hey. how is it going?
RUTH:
Hi.
These are for you.
Thank you.
Are you kissing the jerk?
-Um. well. this is Ledger.
-(chuckles)
Ledjerk.
-Oh. Ledjerk. (chuckles)
-KENNA: Hmm.
Okay. She's funny and vicious.
I'm Ledjerk.
(Ledger chuckles)
-Ah. Right. Okay.
-(Kenna chuckles)
♪ ♪
Can you tell me
what happened that night?
Ledger. please.
I need to know.
(sighs heavily)
I'll read it to you.
♪ ♪
"Dear Scotty:
"We went to our favorite spot
that night.
(Scotty and Kenna laughing)
KENNA:
"By our favorite lake.
my side of town."
(Scotty and Kenna laughing)
KENNA:
Mm.
"Because it was your birthday.
I wanted it to be special."
(both laughing)
Mm-mm.
Don't make me do it alone.
(chuckles):
Come on.
-Mmm.
-Mm-hmm.
(both laughing)
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Okay. Here we go.
-(Kenna laughing)
-I'm gonna get in there.
-(water splashing)
-Whoo-hoo!
It's not--
it's really not that bad.
-It really isn't. -(laughs)
Wait for me. Wait for me.
-SCOTTY: Whoo. baby!
-(squeals)
-(laughing)
-Oh. my God!
-(squeals)
-(chuckles)
Oh. my God. (sighs)
♪ ♪
Thank you.
You saved me tonight.
And I always will.
I love you.
I love you. too.
Happy birthday.
-(chuckles)
-Mm-hmm.
You know what sounds
really good right now?
What?
Some meat loaf
and mashed potatoes.
(chuckles)
-So. let's go to the diner.
-Mm-hmm.
(both chuckling)
KENNA: "I think we felt
invincible that night."
-("Yellow" by Coldplay playing)
-SCOTTY: ♪ You do ♪
(singing along):
♪ Yeah. they were all yellow ♪
(Kenna laughing)
♪ I came along ♪
♪ I wrote a song for you ♪
(both singing along):
♪ And all the things you do ♪
♪ And it was called
"Yellow..." ♪
-(tires squealing)
-SCOTTY: Kenna!
-(grunting)
-(music distorts. stops)
-(engine clicking)
-(crickets chirping)
-(grunts)
-(metal creaking)
(panting)
Hey.
Scotty?
(strained grunting)
(panting)
(grunts)
(glass tinkling)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(groans)
(panting)
Hey.
Hey. Scotty.
Hey. Hey.
I'm here.
(strained grunting)
(frustrated grunt)
Babe.
Scotty!
(panting)
(whimpers)
(crying):
No!
(ragged panting)
(retches. coughs)
(panting)
No.
(groans)
Help!
"I had to get help.
so I went to the highway."
-(truck horn honking)
-Hey. Help!
No.
Oh!
"No one stopped.
(heart beating steadily)
And that's the last thing
I remember."
(exhales)
(heartbeat continues)
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
(siren wailing faintly)
OFFICER:
How much did you have to drink?
Are you on
any other illegal substances?
Did you call for help?
Did you know he was still alive
when you fled the scene?
when we found him?
(muffled scream)
(cell door clanks)
KENNA: "I didn't know that
your arm had been crushed.
"That you were still alive.
"I'm sorry. Scotty.
"I'm so sorry.
"When the judge gave me
seven years.
"I didn't think it was enough.
"But if I had known
that I was pregnant.
"I would've never pled guilty.
"I just didn't know I had
anything left to live for.
(sniffles)
"There was a 'before you.'
there was a 'during you.'
and I never thought
there would be an 'after you.'"
(breathes deeply)
(sniffles)
♪ ♪
I'm sorry you lost him.
No one's ever said that
to me before.
(sniffles)
(breathes shakily)
(both sigh)
(door opens)
PATRICK:
Hey. hey.
Grace didn't hear back.
She wanted me to check on you.
Oh.
(scoffs)
Patrick.
He was your... best friend.
LEDGER:
Patrick.
Patrick. Patrick!
♪ ♪
(dogs barking in distance)
Patrick.
Are you sleeping with her?
Look. I think the three of us
need to sit down and just...
Are you sleeping with her?
We've all been wrong about her.
You've taken
the worst moment of her life
and made it into who she is.
(panting)
(grunting)
Oh. my God.
(spits)
-GRACE: Oh. my... No.
-DIEM: Ledger!
-LEDGER: Patrick!
-Ledger!
PATRICK:
Get her in.
Patrick. Just...
Leave us alone.
-Hear me out!
-Leave us alone.
(sighs)
(spits)
(panting)
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
You love her?
(sighs heavily)
Well... well. I just hope
you do the right thing.
What's the right thing?
I don't know.
I just hope you do it.
-(snickers)
-(chuckles) Ow.
(inhales sharply)
♪ ♪
(knock on door)
What happened?
Was it Patrick?
Did Diem see?
No. No.
No. this can't...
Are they gonna let you see her?
I don't know. I-I honestly
don't know what's gonna happen.
-Oh. God.
-(sighs) Kenna.
I have to-- Sorry.
I have to leave.
Wait.
Kenna. No.
I just-- I don't. I don't want
things to change for her.
Her life is-is so happy.
and she doesn't even know
that I exist.
You should just give them
some time. all right?
Give them time?
They've had fucking years.
Okay?
They're not gonna get over it.
I mean. what's gonna change?
-It's only gonna get harder
for us. -(sighs) Kenna.
-Wait. wait. wait.
-(panting)
Please don't go.
Just go to them and apologize.
Diem needs you. (sighs)
Kenna. no. Kenna.
-Ke-- Stay.
-Please get...
Please don't go.
Please. Please.
Okay?
No.
♪ ♪
I can't stay here.
(sniffles)
Please don't hate them.
They're giving her a good life.
When Diem asks about her mom.
I'm gonna make sure she knows
how incredible you are.
And how much you love her.
(sniffling)
KENNA (whispers):
Goodbye.
(both sigh)
(sniffles)
(breathing heavily)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
You should go.
This won't take long.
I've given the last five years
of my life to that little girl.
You owe me this.
This is Kenna's.
I bookmarked the letter
I need you to read.
The rest is private.
I don't want you to read
this letter because...
because I love Kenna.
I want you to read this letter
because Scotty loved Kenna.
He really loved her.
(breathing heavily)
Here.
(door closes)
♪ ♪
What do you think. Ivy?
You want to come with me?
(Ivy squeaks)
(knock on door)
Can we talk?
You can come in.
Um...
I read what you wrote
about that night.
I guess...
♪ ♪
...I do believe...
...Scotty...
...would have wanted you
to meet...
(sighs)
...his daughter.
I can't promise anything
beyond that.
(sobs softly. sniffles)
("Yellow" by
Morgan Harper-Jones playing)
♪ Look at the stars ♪
♪ Look how they shine for you ♪
♪ And everything you do ♪
♪ They were all yellow ♪
♪ I swam across ♪
♪ I jumped across for you ♪
♪ Oh. what a thing to do ♪
♪ It was all yellow ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
-♪ Ooh. ooh. ♪
-(song fades)
I invited Kenna to dinner.
Would you like to join?
♪ ♪
She's out back.
(grunts. giggles)
Can you come with me?
DIEM:
Ledger!
Hey. (chuckles) Come here.
Whoa.
I missed you so much.
I want you to meet somebody.
This is my friend Kenna.
-Hi. Kenna.
-(Ledger chuckles)
Do you want to see
my pet turtle?
I would love to.
What's his name?
Ledger. It looks just like him.
-Hey.
-(Diem chuckles)
(Kenna chuckles)
(Diem chuckles)
-KENNA: Oh. wow.
-(Ledger chuckles)
(chuckling)
Do you want to see
my jungle gym?
I'm really nearly six.
and it's my gift.
so it's not a very good surprise
'cause it's too big to wrap.
(Kenna chuckles)
Ledger. can you put Ledger
in his tank
-so he doesn't get lost?
-(chuckles)
LEDGER:
All right.
Oh. You handsome beast.
-(chuckles)
-(Diem laughing)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
This used to be my daddy's.
You know. I-I used to know
your daddy.
Were you his friend?
I was his girlfriend.
(chuckles) I didn't know
my daddy had a girlfriend.
(laughs. sniffles)
Yeah. I loved him very much.
Why are you sad?
Do you miss him?
Um... (sighs. sniffles)
Well. I miss...
I miss him a lot.
But it's not why I'm crying.
I'm crying because I'm so happy
to be here with you.
Why?
Can you come here? (sniffles)
I want to tell you something.
I know that
you just met me. but...
W-Well. I'm your mama.
Really?
Yeah. you. um...
you grew inside my belly.
and then. um.
Nana and Grandpa. they...
Not Grandpa. NoNo.
(laughs):
Oh. NoNo.
NoNo and Nana... (sniffles)
they took care of you
when I couldn't.
Did you get a bigger car?
Um...
Right. Um... (chuckles)
Well. I'm working on it.
What drink do you want?
(chuckles) Can I ha--
I'd like a purple one. please.
It's purple-lavender.
I'm gonna get you
a piece of toast.
Thank you.
Mmm!
I forgot your name.
(inhales sharply)
Um. Kenna.
Can you push me on the swings.
please. Kenna?
Yes.
(sniffles)
Whee!
(chuckling)
Hey.
(laughing)
Uh. she's looking for
some juice. (sighs)
Mm. in the fridge.
-Okay.
-(sniffles)
Can I help with anything?
(voice breaking):
No. that's okay.
You play with your daughter.
(Grace sniffles)
Uh. G-Grace.
It's... (crying)
♪ ♪
We go forward.
(sighs)
-(Diem chuckles) -She thought
that she had to wear a cast
for the rest of her life.
No one thought to tell her...
GRACE:
And she was only three.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
I've known you since
you were Diem's age. Ledge.
And not one time
in all those years
did you ever give me
a single reason to doubt you.
So if you're telling me
Kenna's worthy of Diem...
...then I believe you.
Are you kidding me?
(pigeon cooing)
(Ledger chuckles)
Is that a freakin' pigeon?
(both laughing)
That's a freakin' pigeon!
LEDGER (laughing):
Wow.
(Patrick coos)
(laughing)
♪ Your skin ♪
♪ Oh. yeah.
your skin and bones ♪
♪ Turn into
something beautiful ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ You know I love you so ♪
(Diem speaks indistinctly)
♪ You know I love you so... ♪
Look.
You sure you don't
want me to help?
-We got this.
-Yeah. we've got this.
(Kenna chuckles)
-♪ Ooh. ooh. ♪
-(song fades)
Gonna stick it in right here.
Why are we putting this here?
(Kenna sighs)
Well. it'll make your nana
really happy
to know that it's here
if she ever drives by.
Will it make my daddy happy?
It'll... it'll make him
so happy that we're together.
Can I hit it?
Yeah. hit it right here.
Good job. (chuckles)
KENNA:
Dear Scotty:
I used to write to you
when I was lonely.
I know it's been a while.
Maybe that's because
I'm not alone anymore.
I have Ledger...
...and your parents
and Diem.
Now the reminders of you
only make me smile.
(Kenna chuckles)
Love. Kenna.
Come here.
Whoa! (laughing)
All right. who wants snow cones?
BOTH:
FofanaLemonana!
-(Kenna laughs)
-(Ledger chuckles)
I think we need music.
-Yes!
-(chuckles)
("Light Over the Hill"
by Noah Cyrus playing)
♪ I keep thinking back
on all I left behind ♪
♪ I keep looking in
the back seat as I drive ♪
♪ 'Cause hope is
a road you can take ♪
♪ When the old one ends ♪
♪ Means you can start again ♪
♪ Start again ♪
♪ And love is the light
coming over the hill ♪
♪ When I look in her eyes.
yeah. it's you I feel ♪
♪ If there's a mountain
to climb or a life to rebuild ♪
♪ Oh. for you. my love ♪
♪ You know I will ♪
(singers vocalizing)
♪ It's hard to think
you could ever be enough ♪
♪ After letting down
all the people that you love ♪
♪ But hope is a boat
when you're lost at sea ♪
♪ When the storm lets go ♪
♪ It'll all come back to me ♪
♪ Yeah. come on back to me ♪
♪ And love is the light
coming over the hill ♪
♪ When I look in her eyes.
yeah. it's you I feel ♪
♪ If there's a mountain
to climb or a life to rebuild ♪
♪ Oh. for you. my love ♪
♪ You know I will ♪
(singers vocalizing)
♪ Oh. love is the light
coming over the hill ♪
♪ And if there's a way.
then you know that I will ♪
♪ When I look in her eyes.
I can feel you still ♪
♪ Oh. love is the light
coming over the hill ♪
♪ Oh. love is a light
coming over the hill. ♪
(singers vocalizing)
(vocalizing continues)
(song ends)
("Letting Go"
by Angie McMahon playing)
♪ I might've spent six months
lying on my living room floor ♪
♪ I might've been sick
then well ♪
♪ Then sick some more ♪
♪ I might be prouder of me ♪
♪ Than I ever have been ♪
♪ I've been learning 'bout
letting go ♪
♪ How to do it without my claws
scratching the surfaces ♪
♪ I've been learning 'bout
wasting time ♪
♪ And closing some doors ♪
♪ Hoping to open more
down the line ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's okay. it's okay ♪
♪ Make mistakes. make mistakes ♪
♪ Make mistakes ♪
♪ Make mistakes. ♪
(song ends)